link-translations.com 2015-02-18

# Privacy Policy | Link Translations

This Privacy Policy contains information about how and when we collect personal information through this website and how we use the information that we collect. This website may contain links to other websites not operated by us. These other websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you subscribe as a freelance linguist or fill out a form to request a no-obligation quote on our services.

When filling out a form or registering as a linguist on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address and phone number. You may, however, visit our site at all times anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the service requested.
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide may be used to send you occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. The email address you provide us during registration will be used to send you emails with news. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you may do so automatically by selecting the “unsubscribe” function within the e-mail.
  * To improve our website  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you
  * To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway provider’s database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Children’s privacy

This website’s online ordering and registration features are intended for use by persons ages 13 and up. We do not establish or maintain registrations for any child whom we know to be under the age of 13. We do not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If we discover that we have received personally identifiable information from an individual who indicates that he or she is, or whom we otherwise have reason to believe is, under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our website privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by using any of the contact information under our “Contact Us” page.
